{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454050081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454050080"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454050455","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454050455"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454050938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454050938"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454051283","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454051283"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454051689","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454051689"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454052166","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454052165"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454052390","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454052390"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454055629","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454055628"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454055664","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454055664"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454056381","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454056381"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454056782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454056781"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454057080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454057080"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454057288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454057288"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454057488","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454057487"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454057808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454057808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454058043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454058043"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454061219","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454061218"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454061623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454061623"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454064210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454064209"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454064433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454064433"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454064644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454064643"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454068160","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454068160"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454071963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454071962"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454072996","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454072995"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454075699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454075699"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454076075","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454076075"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454076562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454076562"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454076912","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454076912"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454077321","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454077321"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454077803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454077803"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454078035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454078035"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454081229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454081229"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454081280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454081280"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454081994","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454081994"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454082389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454082389"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454082683","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454082683"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454082887","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454082887"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454083082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454083081"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454083398","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454083397"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454083621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454083621"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454086261","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454086259"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454086345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454086345"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 58f373f0-4aca-4bdc-b1e3-daab3ce17bc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454105287","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454105287"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" ca4e4740-6c57-492b-b3be-f797a0d1f6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-7-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454110197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454110197"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" ca4e4740-6c57-492b-b3be-f797a0d1f6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_0-8-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454117630","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454117630"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" ca4e4740-6c57-492b-b3be-f797a0d1f6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-2-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454123677","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454123677"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" ca4e4740-6c57-492b-b3be-f797a0d1f6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-0-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454130448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454130448"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" ca4e4740-6c57-492b-b3be-f797a0d1f6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_2-3-9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454137140","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454137140"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" ca4e4740-6c57-492b-b3be-f797a0d1f6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_4-3-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454145241","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454145241"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" ca4e4740-6c57-492b-b3be-f797a0d1f6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-0-9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454152000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454152000"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" ca4e4740-6c57-492b-b3be-f797a0d1f6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-6-0"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454158388","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454158388"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" ca4e4740-6c57-492b-b3be-f797a0d1f6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-6-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454165081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454165081"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" ca4e4740-6c57-492b-b3be-f797a0d1f6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_0-6-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454171755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454171755"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" ca4e4740-6c57-492b-b3be-f797a0d1f6f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.39"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_6_0-6-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454194020","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454194020"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 3cb2d209-3131-4d62-9b7e-8b42f84f4141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_N_H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454200707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454200707"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 3cb2d209-3131-4d62-9b7e-8b42f84f4141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_N_F"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454207366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454207366"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 3cb2d209-3131-4d62-9b7e-8b42f84f4141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_O_E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454214043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454214043"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 3cb2d209-3131-4d62-9b7e-8b42f84f4141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_P_Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454220702","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454220701"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 3cb2d209-3131-4d62-9b7e-8b42f84f4141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_F_R"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454227394","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454227394"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 3cb2d209-3131-4d62-9b7e-8b42f84f4141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_K_W_N"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454234059","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454234058"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 3cb2d209-3131-4d62-9b7e-8b42f84f4141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_N_P"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454240728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454240728"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 3cb2d209-3131-4d62-9b7e-8b42f84f4141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_N_Y"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454247457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454247457"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 3cb2d209-3131-4d62-9b7e-8b42f84f4141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_N_D"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454254150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454254150"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 3cb2d209-3131-4d62-9b7e-8b42f84f4141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_N_G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454267310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454267309"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 3cb2d209-3131-4d62-9b7e-8b42f84f4141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_Y_N_G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454306174","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454306174"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 382fd5ce-f19a-414e-a876-c0322672c9ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454327444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454327444"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 382fd5ce-f19a-414e-a876-c0322672c9ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454329895","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454329895"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 382fd5ce-f19a-414e-a876-c0322672c9ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454354650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454354650"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 382fd5ce-f19a-414e-a876-c0322672c9ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454357185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454357185"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 382fd5ce-f19a-414e-a876-c0322672c9ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454405188","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454405188"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 382fd5ce-f19a-414e-a876-c0322672c9ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454434726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454434726"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 382fd5ce-f19a-414e-a876-c0322672c9ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454454984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454454984"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 382fd5ce-f19a-414e-a876-c0322672c9ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549454455188","data":{"timestamp":" 1549454455188"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_145338"," gameId":" 382fd5ce-f19a-414e-a876-c0322672c9ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}